[{"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Do you ever think we'd be sitting here by the pool of the Beverly Hilton doing an interview about your Oscar nomination?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "You know, its an honor, it's a thrill all of the above.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "And to be Oscar nominated, what is that mean to you as an artist?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Are you going to pretend like everybody else I've interviewed that you haven't written a winner's speech yet?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "I mean this instance it will be one person.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "Who when you really think about it that you personally most thankful too?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Well, you know, he and his mate, his neighbor, the Arch, as they call him ...", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "Was he the greatest figure of your lifetime?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Well, she only saw or heard me sing once and on the stage just before she passed away.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "What would your mother have made of you of the Oscars?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "It certainly is, Bono.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "That's what you're missing and defiance is the essence of romance, isn't it Piers?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "Gosh.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "If I had the power to let you relive one moment in your life outside of marriage and children, which one would you choose?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "Playing on stage for that time in front of all of my school friends and indeed my mother in the audience if you asked because that bond (inaudible).", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "What's the one -- what's the one if I said, I can -- you can have that again tonight?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "Did I finally found what I'm looking for ...", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "Finally, did you ever find what you're looking for?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "Is it Vivienne Westwood again?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "I don't know any -- I don't think anyone can take down Bono.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "Can you do that?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "None of those views are mine.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "So what's happens?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "That's the thing, it's like asking ...", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "That moment if you win and you go the Oscars podium, who will you feel most thankful to in your life for helping bring you to that moment?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "Definitely the omniscient because that's where it all comes from.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "In that moment if you won, when you look back at your entire life who will you feel most thankful to?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "There's a long list of people who got me to where I am right now.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "And who down here?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "So many faces.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "When you're standing there potentially is an Oscar winner, who will come in to your head?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "My mom and my Dad for sure.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "Any family?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "ILLIAMS: I couldn't because all of these things are -- every second is a piece in the mosaic for this moment.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "Which moment would be the greatest moment of you life so far?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "When I first met my wife.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "You can do it all over again?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "Over my buddy Alex's house down in a -- down in (inaudible).", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "When was that?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "I knew it.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "And how am I going to land her?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "It doesn't feel surreal I mean it feels very real it's happening, and I understand what's happening, I'm aware of what's happening.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "How do you feel about this extraordinary resurgence?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "I tweeted the other day, are you on Twitter?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "That's -- yeah.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "Is that the key?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "Well, I've got thanks -- I've got my own personal thanks to God, I've got my own personal thanks to family in many respects, the family I've got now, the family I came from, and I've got another little secret thank for somebody I know very well that I might share if I was so fortunate to.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "Who are the key people when you look back over the whole time that you would feel most thankful to?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not -- I'm -- look, I'm not there yet so ...", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "What do you think you'll feel when you're standing there if you get that?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "... I really haven't thought about what I would feel.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "But if you do, how would you feel?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "Any moment.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "Replay that -- just any moment?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "One you'd most like to live through again.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "The greatest moment?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "CCONAUGHEY: Courage, integrity, you know, anybody loses a father that's the main crutch in a man's life, and he's there for a reason because, you know, if it ever comes down to it you got, you know, my father would lean up against me.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "What impact did that have on you?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "He'd love it.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "So what's your father have made of you being Oscar nominee?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Can you quite believe it?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "Go to Mexico and drink the water.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "How I can lose 43 pounds quickly?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "It feels so incredible.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Merry, how does that feel?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "LAYTON: Well, you know, when I was singing background I always felt like I was center stage.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "Do you two, do you prefer to backing singers or has the dream always been, Merry, to be center stage yourself?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "I was just so young.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "How do you feel when you see that?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Well, it was so unexpected.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "The kind of moment like that where you hear Stevie Wonder or Ray Charles or whoever it maybe bestowing that kind of comment, that honor on you?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "Is it -- you've been Oscar-nominated because love the idea ...", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "Are you kidding?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "Well, as I said earlier, it was always me.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "Do you feel a little bit of \"why not me\"?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "It was always me, you know, I mean if I'm giving my heart as I said in the film and my soul to your project, I come in -- excuse me, can I say this?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "Do you -- let me ask you one thing before we get another break?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Do you ever have, either of you, do ever have big stars, you don't have to name them if you don't want to, have asked you not to sing too well so you don't eclipse them?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "I think that what I meant is background singing is such an awesome thing and you can really get into it and you learn from so many different people.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "What did you mean by that?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "Well, you know, Piers, I'm still trying to figure that one out and I mean for so many years you work with all these great, great people and they won't do it without you.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "What is that X factor, for one of the better phrase that takes you from being just a singer to being a star do you think?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "Mine was the moment that I worked with Ray Charles in Carnegie Hall.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "What's has been the moment if I could say you could relive it right now?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "Definitely singing with Michael \"I Just Can't Stop Loving You\", the duet and to sing him \"This Close\" that was definitely the pinch me moment.", "docId": "140214pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "Judith, what would yours be?", "qSentId": 627}]